Exercise 1-13. Individual Practice. Practice saying the sentences after the
suggestion and the beep tone. You'll be given only a short time in which to reply,
so you won't have the leisure to overthink. Start speaking as soon as you
hear the tone, because I'll be saying the sentence only a few seconds later. 1.
Convey the information that it really does sound as if rain is falling.
2. Convey the opinion that, although it has the sound of rain, it may be something else.
3. Convey the different feelings that someone has about rain and snow.
4. Convey the fact that rain is an impossibility right now.
Practice the four sentences on your own ten times. Once you're familiar with
moving the stress around and feeling how the meaning changes, continue with the
next exercise.